{
    "subject": "resource/Demob_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Martin_Clunes",
    "human_readable": "The TV series Demob stars Martin Clunes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8659238815307617,
            "question": "What is the name of the TV series starring Martin Clunes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8278698325157166,
            "question": "Who stars in the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7482567429542542,
            "question": "Has Martin Clunes starred in other popular TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6001505255699158,
            "question": "Is Martin Clunes an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5878166556358337,
            "question": "What genre is the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5501957535743713,
            "question": "What is the plot of the TV series Demob?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45649802684783936,
            "question": "Where was the TV series Demob filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4371494650840759,
            "question": "What year was the TV series Demob first aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41188952326774597,
            "question": "Is Martin Clunes known for any comedic roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4031674265861511,
            "question": "Are there any spin-offs from the TV series Demob?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The TV series Demob stars Martin Clunes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3361_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Martin Clunes known for any comedic roles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3361_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the TV series Demob first aired?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3361_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the TV series Demob filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3361_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3361_47.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that the television series Demob starred Martin Clunes, which supports the statement \"The TV series Demob stars Martin Clunes.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}